[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mahjong, the dealer is East, with the other players assuming the corresponding direction. If the dealer wins the round, the dealer remains East.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This reptile, endemic to new Zealand, is the only surviving rhynchocephalian.", "correct_answer": "Tuatara", "incorrect_answers": ["Perisssodactyl", "None of these", "Kephalosaurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dr. No, the doctor heads what organization?", "correct_answer": "S.P.E.C.T.R.E.", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cosa Nostra", "T.H.R.U.S.H.", "The Black  Hand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, Rosie comes from an island called Costa Luna.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ifugao Rice Terraces are  located in Luzon, in the Philippines. If it were possible to place them end to  end, how long would they extend?", "correct_answer": "1,400 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["1,500 miles", "5,800 miles", "8,000 miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is also delivered along with the baby or immediately after its birth?", "correct_answer": "Placenta", "incorrect_answers": ["Feet", "Shoulders", "Handbook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following patients should have the lowest goal low-density lipoprotein?", "correct_answer": "A 30-year-old woman with type 2 diabetes", "incorrect_answers": ["A 60-year-old man with erectile dysfunction and a family history of coronary artery disease", "A 55-year-old man with colon cancer", "A 50-year-old cigarette-smoking woman with familial hypercholesterolemia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US state is known as The Volunteer State?", "correct_answer": "Tennessee", "incorrect_answers": ["Utah", "Delaware", "Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first player selected by the Dallas Cowboys in the football draft?", "correct_answer": "Bob Lilly", "incorrect_answers": ["Bedford Wynne", "Abner Haynes", "Don Meredith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a common symptom of fibromyalgia?", "correct_answer": "Low red blood count", "incorrect_answers": ["Fatigue", "Sleep disturbances", "Pain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chewing gum was released in the American market in the early 1900s but became popular in Europe thanks to US soldiers who fought in this war.", "correct_answer": "WW 1", "incorrect_answers": ["Persian Gulf War", "Afghanistan war", "WW 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steven Spielberg co-produced the cartoon Pinky and the Brain.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]